SPEAKER_00 : Sportcon for Prod. Aventure. Go ahead.
SPEAKER_00 : Awe, yes, sir.
SPEAKER_00 : C V E M port side going to Phrasir Pantoang terminal.
SPEAKER_00 : Ah, yes, P V thirty-four, correct, formative.
SPEAKER_00 : Stubborn twenty.  It's okay, Copy that.  Thank you for Your information.
SPEAKER_00 : Not fun out there.  Okay. we Have a good day.
SPEAKER_00 : Sever ten.
SPEAKER_00 : Proper million liberties.
SPEAKER_00 : They have a lot of money.
SPEAKER_00 : Bicking zero six For make zero six for.
SPEAKER_00 : West Control,  West Control Coastalist Adventure,  calling.
SPEAKER_00 : Ah, yes, sir. May I know the misunderame?  Passing.
SPEAKER_00 : Provincial Coast Guard Island Continental Coast Guard Island, Washington, D. C.
SPEAKER_00 : and figure.
SPEAKER_00 : Roger Weigelmuss, Attention Coastalist, calling.
SPEAKER_00 : Yes, pilot, you can go Navigation Cemetery in the starboard tower pilot.
SPEAKER_00 : Roger, thank you.
SPEAKER_00 : teammer, keep The Shipping Team on team.
SPEAKER_01 : the socialist movement to the What Is Your misunderination?
SPEAKER_01 : Maybe that you are going transferring the number to percentage of feet that is formed. Is that correct?
SPEAKER_01 : Bridge on the machine, this is the one bus there in front Of you for reign liberty and caution when you Proceed to The John Family.
SPEAKER_01 : this is the one bus speed one or ten.
SPEAKER_01 : The bus is on the right.
SPEAKER_01 : Body travel.
SPEAKER_01 : Bridge travels for travels.
SPEAKER_01 : Roger that, teacher. vessel is operational.
SPEAKER_01 : this vessel is a vessel on the left,  or both sides,  will Have been V guard master.  repeat the promptly name is to be guard master.
SPEAKER_01 : this vessel is A ventura,  bigger Purchase by log.
SPEAKER_01 : This vessel is a Purchase-based vessel, and is located in the Purchase area.
SPEAKER_01 : The area is open.
SPEAKER_01 : The back Alloy is a Vigamost.
SPEAKER_01 : Bridge the rest of our to the young second.
SPEAKER_01 : His Immediate Pleasure.
SPEAKER_01 : He Further Assures to the French Consulate.
SPEAKER_01 : Yes, good morning, pilot. this is the French Consulate.  You want to go to Proceed Painted Terminal,  that thought We Passed a Swim with Fever Mass tower suburb.
SPEAKER_01 : Okay,  thank you.
SPEAKER_01 : Theorism.  Theorism.  Theorism.
SPEAKER_01 : keep A. l. lngtank.
SPEAKER_01 : Amco Pride,  traveled coastalist colony, Mid-Safe.
SPEAKER_01 : Yes,  sir,  later we pass starboard.  Starboard.
SPEAKER_01 : Yes,  sir.  Round two, taunting starboard starboard.
SPEAKER_01 : Starboard ten.
SPEAKER_01 : Chesting transfer known it should be clear. By checking transfer known it should be clear.
SPEAKER_01 : For twenty.
SPEAKER_01 : Starboard twenty.
SPEAKER_01 : Support thanks. It's Your problem there too.
SPEAKER_01 : Clearse the focus and oversture.
SPEAKER_01 : Author Fessel,  K. M. Assure,  K. M. S Yourne Assure,  at Fenn Coursule, Scotland.
SPEAKER_01 : West Control and Fenn Coursule is calling.
SPEAKER_01 : Yes,  question, sir. For motto festival,  Q. and S. S. Ashore,  where is he going?
SPEAKER_01 : Roger Kofi,  thank you.
SPEAKER_01 : This Loot.  The this?
SPEAKER_01 : This afternoon.
SPEAKER_01 : Okey ma roo, starboard ten.
SPEAKER_01 : Bridge, govek to propose channel.
SPEAKER_01 : Marine Liberty, Marine Liberty,  Earthquake from Coastalist Calling.
SPEAKER_01 : Oh, Shaggy. May I know where All is going?
SPEAKER_01 : Roger Goping, Peter King Nine.  So later I'll We pass you On Port Side.
SPEAKER_01 : The Peter before,  right?
SPEAKER_01 : Million For team going to Weep team in nine.
SPEAKER_01 : be nine here.
SPEAKER_01 : Make three one nine. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01 : Okay. Nice.
SPEAKER_01 : Maybe current from there to this way.
SPEAKER_01 : the promptly noisy swing.
SPEAKER_01 : Its area is called the Illinois Crossings area.
SPEAKER_01 : The area is called the Illinois Crossings area.
SPEAKER_00 : Mhm?
SPEAKER_00 : We do A first part. Welcome.
SPEAKER_00 : and and All right. and in
SPEAKER_00 : the team.
SPEAKER_00 : The team is in this area.
SPEAKER_00 : their location is in this area.
SPEAKER_00 : and the location is in this area.
SPEAKER_00 : Hump Coupe.
SPEAKER_00 : Bridge,  starboard.
SPEAKER_00 : Okay, transferring your name and surname.
SPEAKER_00 : Thank you, transferring your name and surname.
SPEAKER_00 : The dock was vague, Lois controlled. All ships were docked on travel.
SPEAKER_00 : Game methods are unique as well.
SPEAKER_00 : Bridge is the tours music website.
SPEAKER_00 : Doctor, are you ready for the tours music website?
SPEAKER_00 : In what form?
SPEAKER_00 : A spotter.
SPEAKER_00 : and the medical school system is available for anybody.
SPEAKER_00 : Bridge authority also crewing travels depending on their speed, transferring nine.
SPEAKER_00 : Yep.
SPEAKER_00 : Tuna.
SPEAKER_00 : Go ahead,  sir, Engine Room Bridge.
SPEAKER_01 : the telephone is now test your telephone.
SPEAKER_02 : Pengin Room Bridge.
SPEAKER_02 : this telegraph tested berth no power. By this telegraph,  the telegraph tested berth no power.
SPEAKER_01 : Okay, good. Let me try again.  Let me try again.
SPEAKER_00 : thanks to the fact that this is the area that needs traveling this is the area that needs traveling, that is why the area is slightly higher.
SPEAKER_00 : Engine room, transportation room.
SPEAKER_01 : Go to this room again.
SPEAKER_00 : Stift engineer,  Bridge.
SPEAKER_00 : Yes,  engine.  Now the engine has power and we can continue to overplan.
SPEAKER_00 : transferting transferting to engine.  Thank you. transferting transferting to engine. transferting transferting to engine. transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting
SPEAKER_00 : Yes,  Penboy,  Hebrew,  Penger.
SPEAKER_00 : Second officer, Weaken Lowering Dunder treatment call.
SPEAKER_00 : West Control Coastalist,  also in travel.
SPEAKER_00 : West Control,  West Control.
SPEAKER_00 : The Coastalist Adventure.
SPEAKER_00 : and continue to Proceeding Three Four.
SPEAKER_00 : Keep All Soon, People Banker.
SPEAKER_04 : No. Up and Down.
SPEAKER_02 : Roger. Up and Down.
SPEAKER_03 : It is our opposition at The Await.
SPEAKER_01 : thanks away The Await. thank you.
SPEAKER_01 : West Control Coastalist Adjacention.
SPEAKER_01 : is the Coastalist Offensive Agency in Western Holdings, British Columbia. Permission channel,  change channel, one hit.
SPEAKER_01 : Costalism control, this is Coastalist offensive intervention.
SPEAKER_01 : Ah, yes, sir, good morning to you. Coastal Are You Surveillance Permission?
SPEAKER_01 : Coming Of Wiscarple Ferry,  going To Proceed Punching On Terminal 3, 4.
SPEAKER_01 : Bridge Punching On Terminal 3, 4.
SPEAKER_01 : transferring transferring transferring transferring transferring transferring transferring transferring transferring
SPEAKER_01 : Bridge transferring transferring transferring transferring transferring transferring
SPEAKER_01 : Oh Toll, transferring Transferring transferring transferring transferring transferring technique.
SPEAKER_01 : Ah,  yes, pilot, standby in March too.  We will quickly On Your Port.
SPEAKER_01 : The video took a lot of time. Translating the video.
SPEAKER_00 : Oka,  chaser team at 1-eight.
SPEAKER_00 : Costal location point to berth is currently on control.
SPEAKER_00 : and waiting for the temperature this stakedly offers two vessels.
SPEAKER_00 : We have 150.
SPEAKER_00 : It is solvent mass, too. Pilot.
SPEAKER_00 : C Loose Adventure is placed near The Purchase Bomb.
SPEAKER_01 : Sophurine bars to coastal surface reporting.
SPEAKER_01 : Yes, pellet, you can go ahead pellet At Our Course, You're Spun.
SPEAKER_01 : Okay, completed. transferred transferred transferred transferred
SPEAKER_01 : Star port, hard to Port.
SPEAKER_01 : Thank you. To be...
SPEAKER_01 : To be team out of our catch in this land.
SPEAKER_01 : Yeah, cool. Before young, in team.
SPEAKER_01 : It's all on Iconic. Trinity.
SPEAKER_01 : Huh?
SPEAKER_00 : Negative. I am waiting for The Depot. I am waiting alongside Andis.
SPEAKER_00 : and Issa.
SPEAKER_00 : Outbands.
SPEAKER_00 : vessel, streetlake location, port music.
SPEAKER_00 : Bridge,  port music.
SPEAKER_02 : Do you have calling Coastalist suspension?
SPEAKER_00 : the crew will misunderubilita in a one minute.
SPEAKER_00 : Chief Engineer,  Chief Engineer,  Bridge Collin.
SPEAKER_00 : thanks to the traveling traveling traveling team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team
SPEAKER_00 : transferting transferting transferting technique transferting transferting transferting transferting transferting
SPEAKER_00 : West Control,  west control, Vesselar, Coastalist.
SPEAKER_00 : airstrip for their information,  our vessel now is a travel engine, transporting engine is now undertaken By travel engine, transfering engine is now undertaken.  Once served, transfering engine is now undertaken.
SPEAKER_00 : Oh, yes, We try To Get Off From John Way, and Please Let Other Faces Know If You Have A Travel Engine. Thank You.
SPEAKER_00 : Thank You. attention.
SPEAKER_00 : How to starboard?
SPEAKER_00 : thanks For Your Support We Not Under Control Now.
SPEAKER_00 : Shide.  Shipt.  Shipping.
SPEAKER_00 : All crew standby All crew standby Bozoon, Bozoon,  Chief officer Standby for Lounge,  the anchor.
SPEAKER_00 : Okay,  please stand by The misunder.
SPEAKER_00 : A second officer coming,  second officer.
SPEAKER_00 : Please make sure to put The Three Black Pall on The Musk.
SPEAKER_00 : Fifteen minutes, sir.  Fifteen minutes.
SPEAKER_00 : All posted, sir.  It's ten by The Starboard and Ke.
SPEAKER_01 : Sir,  thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir
SPEAKER_02 : . thanks, sir. thanks, sir. thanks, sir.
SPEAKER_00 : Chief engineer, transferred to this colony.
SPEAKER_00 : Ah,  yes transferred to this colony.  How now, transferred transferred to this colony.
SPEAKER_00 : and tagged the colony.
SPEAKER_01 : Bridge Media.
SPEAKER_02 : Bridge Media, transferring from California to California.
SPEAKER_00 : West Coast for Coastalist channelfention calling.
SPEAKER_00 : Roger that, transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transfer
SPEAKER_00 : gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin gevengin ge
SPEAKER_00 : Shief Engineer, this is Colin.
SPEAKER_00 : Vesselon,  Vesselon,  Leicester,  Leicester,  Vesselon,  Leicester,   Leicester,   Leicester,   Leicester,   Leicester,   Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Le
SPEAKER_00 : icester,     Leicester,     Leicester,     Leicester,     Leicester,     Leicester,     Leicester,     Leicester,     Leicester,     Leicester,     Leicester,     Leicester,     Leicester,     Leicester,     Leicester,     Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,    Leicester,
SPEAKER_00 : Translating  transferring   Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Transferring  Trans
SPEAKER_00 : Vessel, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control, vessel control
SPEAKER_00 : are registered for Your information, We cannot verify our engine and We alreadybeform to My office to required assistance.
SPEAKER_00 : Yes,  low anchor near  the bucomm island,   the fort bucomm beacon,   the fort cardinal.
SPEAKER_00 : Awe, yes, sir. Appomatto.
SPEAKER_00 : Bridge Engine Room,  please.
SPEAKER_02 : Sir,  engine can We try to set the main engine  please standby.
SPEAKER_01 : Roger p Vista, transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred transferred
SPEAKER_01 : Okay, is the engine ready,  please?  Start the engine And We Can Try!